http://www.wyomingnews.com/site/privacy.html

Home
Wyomingnews.com respects the privacy of visitors to our site. This privacy policy governs the use and collection of information from you by Cheyenne Newspapers, Inc., and its affiliates ("we" or "us") through your use of this website. This privacy policy does not apply to any information you may provide to us through other means; for example, at a live event, via mail, or via telephone. Please read this privacy policy carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices. By visiting this website, you agree that your visit, and any dispute over our online privacy practices, is governed by this privacy policy and our visitor agreement.Questions regarding privacy issues should be directed to webdesign@wyomingnews.comChildren's PrivacyChildren should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We won't knowingly allow anyone under 13 to register with any of our sites or to provide any other personally identifying information.Types Of Information We CollectThe information we gather falls into two categories: (1) personally-identifying information (for example, your name and address), such as the information you voluntarily supply when you register or initiate transactions, and (2) information gathered on usage patterns and preferences as visitors navigate through our sites. In some cases, it is an agent or affiliate of ours that collects the information on our behalf. Third party providers featured on or linked to by our websites, such as vendors of products and services offered through our sites, may be gathering the same kinds of information.Registration InformationTo make use of certain features on our websites (initiate a subscription transaction, or post a classified ad) visitors need to register and to provide certain information as part of the registration process. We may also ask for information from those who buy products or services or conduct other transactions on our websites. (we may ask, for example, for your name, email address, sex, age, zip code or credit card number, and we might request information on your interest in sports, personal finance, the performing arts, and the like.) The information you supply will help us to offer you more personalized features, to tailor our website to your interests and make them more useful to you, and to process e-commerce transactions.The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. But if you don't supply the information we need, we may be unable to provide you with services we make available to other visitors to our sites.From time to time, we may offer contests, sweepstakes or other promotions on our sites. If you enter one of these promotions, you'll have to provide information about yourself (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address) so that we can contact you if you win. We may share this information with any co-sponsor of the promotion, which we will identify in the official rules. If you don't want us to collect the information requested in the registration form or to provide it to contest co-sponsors, please do not enter the contest or sweepstakes.Cookies. To help make our sites more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we may use a standard feature of browser software, called a "cookie," to assign each visitor a unique, random number, a sort of user id, if you will, that resides on your computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify the visitor, just the computer that a visitor uses to access our site. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we won't know who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie can't read unrelated data off your hard drive. Our advertisers and the third parties that provide products or services through our sites may also assign their own cookies to your browser, a process that we don't control.We may use cookies to help us tailor our site to your needs, to deliver a better, more personalized service. For example, we may use cookies to avoid showing you the same ad, repeatedly, during a single visit. In addition, we may use cookies to track the pages on our sites visited by our users. We can build a better site if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often. Of course, you can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other visitors to our sites.Other methods of collecting information. Our web pages may contain electronic images (called "single-pixel gifs" or "web beacons") that allow us and our vendors to count users who have visited particular pages or to access certain cookies. We may use these tools and other technologies to recognize which pages users visit, and which links they click on. We may also be able to verify your online purchases from us or from third party sites that have agreed to share such information with us.IP addresses. Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit our sites. (your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the internet know where to send you data -- such as the web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally to us. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our sites to the interests of our users, and to measure traffic within our sites.Why We Want To KnowAs with any business, it's important for us to know our customers -- their needs, their likes, what they want and expect from us. Unlike most businesses, however, we deliver a valuable product to our customers without asking for anything in return. It's like prime-time television, only better for you!Since we make most of this website available without charge to you, we rely heavily on advertisers to produce the income necessary to operate our site. Advertisers are like most people: they expect something in return for the money they spend. They want to know how many people will see their ad and how often -- in other words, how effective their ad is likely to be. So it's important that we be able to tell advertisers who our audience is.Disclosure Of InformationAdvertisers. Without your permission, we will not share the personally identifying information you provide when registering with advertisers on our website. We will, however, take the information you provide and aggregate it with data from all the other people that use this website and associated services. Then we will use that pool of information to inform our advertisers about our audience without identifying you personally. For example, we'll be able to say to an advertiser: "we have 3,470 readers in this zip code," which happens to be very close to your location.Vendors and service providers. To make our sites more valuable to our visitors, we may offer some features in conjunction with other providers. Our email services and online classifieds for example, may be made available through cooperative arrangements with providers that specialize in operating such services. In some instances, these third party providers will have the same access to your information as we do. Their use of the information will be subject to the terms of their respective privacy policies, which you can find on their websites.Statistical information. Much of the information we collect is in the form of aggregated statistics, such as the traffic that visits various pages within our sites, and the habits and preferences of our audience. Such aggregated information does not include any information that would identify you personally. We may use such aggregated information and disclose it to third parties as we see fit.Sites to which we link. Of course, our website includes links to plenty of other websites, and provide access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we don't control. When you access another website or purchase products or services or conduct other transactions through our websites, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you're visiting or the provider of such products or services.Other disclosures. We may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our visitor agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our sites, the public, or our company and its employees and agents. As our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that our company, or the bulk of our assets relating to this website, is acquired by another company, information on our visitors would be among the transferred assets.Storage Of InformationMost information gathered on our website is encrypted for storage within a database operated by us or by a contractor on our behalf. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.Changes To This Privacy PolicyA final note: the web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we'll post the changes before they take effect.
Latest News
Assistance program will help businesses impacted by reduced hours
The people's favorite festive cowboys
Wimbledon champ, Tennis Hall of Famer Alex Olmedo dead at 84
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
News Updates
Would you like to receive our daily news? Sign up today!
Please enter a valid email address.
Sign up
Manage your lists
Real-time Stocks
Market Data by TradingView
© Copyright 2020 Wyoming Tribune Eagle, 702 W. Lincolnway Cheyenne, WY
Terms of Service | Privacy | Guidelines for Freelancers
